<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<ModMetaData>
    <name>Sleepy's Weapons - Volume One</name>
    <author>Sleepy068</author>
    <url>https://github.com/sleepy068/Rimworld_Weapons</url>
    <packageId>sleepy068.weaponsvol1</packageId>
    <supportedVersions>
		<li>1.4</li>
		<li>1.5</li>
    </supportedVersions>

    <description>
	
[h2]Sleepy's Weapons - Volume 1 - Germany (v1.0.2)[/h2]
[img]https://i.imgur.com/VqBb1wc.png[/img]

I love to add content to this game that I feel is missing or that I'd like expanded. I figure that if I enjoy what I've added, others may too so I to post my mods to the workshop. Balance is critical to me as I am a vanilla player and I'll try to ensure nothing is unbalanced but ultimately I have a goal in mind for the content I am adding so what I consider balanced may not always be what you'd consider balanced. Hopefully you enjoy the mod none the less.

You can find the stats of all weapons added by all my 'Sleepy's Weapons' mods here:

[img]https://i.imgur.com/DbnM7jC.png[/img]
[b]What Does This Mod Add?[/b]
Adds a total of 47 new weapons. This volume is inspired by weapons made in or by Germany.
Adds 10 new craftable weapons and 37 non-craftable weapons. Not all weapons are made to be crafted to prevent recipe bloat and to add content that to try and always keeps the game fresh by finding weapons.

[img]https://i.imgur.com/AtS9W8r.png[/img]
[img]https://i.imgur.com/XASroqZ.png[/img]
[img]https://i.imgur.com/eNWCqVa.png[/img]
[img]https://i.imgur.com/QEiYijH.png[/img]
[img]https://i.imgur.com/Qgl33ZW.png[/img]
[img]https://i.imgur.com/ykOkzFn.png[/img]
[img]https://i.imgur.com/RhC8Jfh.png[/img]

All weapons were rendered, modified and cleaned up in Adobe Flash from pictures. I did start by drawing the weapons but it was a massive time sink for almost no reward (you just cant see the detail in vanilla rimworld). Instead, I preferred to spend the time balancing the weapons instead.

[img]https://i.imgur.com/ss8ZNXk.png[/img]
[b]Roadmap:[/b]
- Feature complete (bug fixes and balancing will be the focus). I have 100s of weapons and dozens of volumes planned but i want you to be able to have smaller packs instead of one massive super pack. I feel it gives the user more choice for what they want. Volumes are limited to 10 craftable weapons and 50 total weapons.

[img]https://i.imgur.com/YySbEPN.png[/img]
[b]On Going Games:[/b]
- Safe to add to an ongoing game
- It will cause issues if removed from an existing save (consider starting a new game to see if you are happy with the content).

[b]Compatibility[/b]
- Combat Extended: Not Compatible (I don't play with this mod sorry).

[b]Integrated Compatibility:[/b]
None at the moment.

[img]https://i.imgur.com/gghc3iQ.png[/img]
[b]Conflicts[/b]
- Combat Extended: Not Compatible (I don't play with this mod sorry).

[img]https://i.imgur.com/31kQWwH.png[/img]
[b]Known Issues[/b]
No known issues.

[img]https://i.imgur.com/WokZwPP.png[/img]
[b]Language Support[/b]
English (Always Latest)(Developed in this Language)

Github:
https://github.com/sleepy068/Rimworld_Weapons

Please post any issue reports to my Github. I appreciate any feedback but please keep in mind I have a goal in mind for the content I am adding so what I consider balanced may not always be what you'd consider balanced.
	
    </description>

    <modDependencies>
	<li>
		<packageId>sleepy068.weaponscore</packageId>
		<displayName>Sleepy's Weapons - Core</displayName>
		<downloadUrl>https://github.com/sleepy068/Rimworld_Weapons</downloadUrl>
		<steamWorkshopUrl>https://steamcommunity.com/sharedfiles/filedetails/?id=2964374073</steamWorkshopUrl>
	</li>
    </modDependencies>
    <modDependenciesByVersion>
    </modDependenciesByVersion>

    <loadAfter>
	<li>sleepy068.weaponscore</li>
    </loadAfter>

    <incompatibleWith>
    </incompatibleWith>
	
</ModMetaData>